[Music]
[Música]
This week we also had a little video
esta semana hemos tenido un videíto
that has raised quite a few
también que ha levantado bastantes
blisters and quite a controversy on the
ampollas y bastante polémica en el Canal
Antonio David Channel and it's a video in which we
de Antonio David y es un vídeo en el que
see Juan sitting in the chair
vemos a Juan sentadito en la silla
telling the teacher about the bad
diciéndole al profe lo que la mala
experience he's having that
experiencia que la pasa que se están
the kids at school are having
metiendo los niños del colegio
as you've seen
cómo lo habéis visto
I'm not talking about other notes I've already
yo no hablo de otros notas Ya te lo he
told you because I just skip straight to the
dicho porque es que paso directamente
password not directly to the password
pasapalabra no directamente pasapalabra
our uncle Because let's call it that
nuestro tío Porque llámese el percal
because I already know the insults
porque ya me sé luego los insultos
because the other day I mentioned it briefly
Porque el otro día lo comenté por encima
With all due respect in the world grandpa
Con todo el respeto del mundo abuelo
right
verdad
being as objective as possible and there have already
siendo lo más objetivo posible y ya te
been comments about not following I don't know And the thing is that I
hayan comentarios de no seguir no sé Y
skip man because it makes me lazy
es que paso tío porque me produce pereza
now I'm going to tell him I'm going to
ya yo se lo voy a decir yo se lo voy a
tell him one thing well two things One is
decir una cosa bueno dos cosas Una
late but well even so I appreciate
llega tarde pero bueno aún así agradezco
that he did it even if he is late
que lo haya hecho aunque llegue tarde
because it was time to thank with
porque ya era hora de agradecer con
certain masks what part is it that you are
ciertas caretas qué parte es la que
grateful for I don't appreciate Juan's
agradeces no agradezco la de Juan
obviously
obviamente
Antonio David was very lukewarm
Antonio David fue muy tibio
I appreciate Juan's But well it's that
agradezco la de Juan Pero bueno es que
Juan always  it was Juan he is very like me he
Juan siempre ha sido Juan es muy como yo
is very Guerrero Okay then Well it
es muy Guerrero Vale entonces Bueno
seems to me that this video is late
me parece que llega tarde este vídeo
but I still appreciate it
pero aún así lo agradezco
and two to the ladies who now well they have been
y dos a las señoras que ahora bueno
crying very hard for a week
llevan una semana llorando muy
okay just to tell you one thing
fuertemente vale solo decirles una cosa
I find it very funny because one of
me resulta muy gracioso porque una de
the things I've heard is that they are
las cosas que he escuchado es que
going to file a complaint because
van a denunciar porque se ha expuesto a
a group of women has exposed themselves, I mean they are throwing for the whole
un grupo de mujeres o sea tiran para el
sexism thing a lot of okay
rollo del sexismo mucho vale
at the police station or the videos correct
en comisaría o los vídeos correcto
that they are going to file a complaint no but
que van a poner una denuncia no pero
But wait wasn't it the second part
Pero espera no era la segunda parte
these ladies who are crying very
estas señoras que están llorando muy
hard and saying that they are going to file
fuertemente y diciendo que van a poner
a complaint because a
la denuncia porque se ha expuesto a un
group of women has exposed themselves as if the fact that you are
grupo de mujeres como si el que fueseis
women or men had some kind of I
mujeres u hombres tuviese algún tipo de
don't know differences
no sé diferencias
Yes nowadays yes but it's this same
Sí hoy en día sí pero es que este mismo
group of women I want to remind you okay
grupo de mujeres quiero recordarles vale
with all the love in the world and with all
con todo el cariño del mundo y con todos
the kisses that I can send you that they have been
los besos que puedo mandarles que llevan
calling me who
un año o más llamándome a mí que también
am also a woman a pet ass
soy mujer mascota
kisser
[__]
that I have come to hear until I
que he llegado a escuchar hasta que
have a problem with Javi that is why I
tengo un lío con Javi que por eso lo
defend him so much
defiendo tanto
to this point
hasta ese punto
I burst into everyone here I am  it's
yo le reviento a todo el mundo aquí
happened very lightly it
se me ha pasado muy liviano
was so significant that we
fue tan significante que nos hemos
found out But anyway what I want to say is that
enterado Pero bueno que quiero decir que
all these ladies who have been
todas estas señoras que llevan todo un
making these types of comments for a whole year or more
año o más haciendo este tipo de
that you then hide behind the fact that they
comentarios que luego escudéis en que os
exposed you in a live broadcast you
han expuesto en un directo
continue crying are people who have
seguís llorando son personas que tienen
thousands of followers no because Well of
miles de Seguidores no porque Bueno
course me obviously I answer regarding
claro yo obviamente Yo contesto respecto
what they've done to me But
a lo que me han hecho a mí Pero
of course
por supuesto
Ah well Yes Lovers and I no
Ah bueno Sí Amantes y yo no
official thanks the rest of us are we are the
oficial las demás somos somos la
room
habitación
concubines
concubinas
But anyway I want to say that the
Pero pero bueno quiero decir que al
rest of the people who follow you have also had it
resto de gente que te sigue también les
fall on them and
ha caído la de Dios y
atesa also the crushed
atesa también las machacado
the yellow weapons for not to mention for not to
las armas amarillas por no hablar por no
mention what they've been doing with
hablar de lo que llevan haciendo con
Marta for a year
Marta un año
how disgusting and here here What happens is that you have to
qué asco y aquí aquí Lo que pasa que hay
have balls when it comes to putting
que tener huevo a la hora de poner las
things no And throw your little hand like this The
cosas no Y tira la manita así La
Little Stone like this a little bit No if you're going to do it
Piedrecita así un poquito No si tú vas a
Do it right damn get there you
hacerlo Hazlo bien [__] cógete ahí que
have material and everything you have the entire
tienes material y todo tienes toda la
newspaper archives in the world to dance and to
hemeroteca del mundo bailar y para
tell things as they are and even if it's
contar las cosas como son y aunque lo
late but you load it in one no It
haga tarde pero te lo cargas de una no
turns out that from what I've gone
Resulta ser que por lo que yo he ido
spinning and from the information that's coming to me it
hilando y por las informaciones que a mí
turns out that one
me vienen llegando Resulta ser que una
of these twitterers who is the one who
de estas tuiteras que es la que más
usually gives Marta the most [ __ ] risk okay
suele meterle [__] a Marta riesgo vale
has a friendship that I imagine it will be I don't
tiene amistad que me imagino que será no
know if it will be a friendship in person Or it is a
sé si será amista en persona O es
friendship of talking every day on
amistad de hablar todos los días por
WhatsApp but a
WhatsApp pero
certain person from the Moreno family from
cierta persona de la familia Moreno de
whom I am waiting for their lawsuit is
la cual estoy esperando su demanda
giving her this [ __ ] for what is
le va metiendo caquita esta para que
luck on social networks Okay then
esta la suerte en redes Vale entonces
This is luck on social networks with the
Esta es la suerte en redes con la
intention of making Marta explode okay
intención de hacer explotar a Marta vale
And many times Well she is teasing her with
Y muchas veces Pues la está picando con
things that maybe
cosas que a lo mejor
the audience doesn't realize the
la audiencia no se da cuenta de las
things that the twitterer is saying
cosas que está soltando la tuitera
because they don't know things or I mean
porque no conocen las cosas o sea
imagine the acne that you and I know
imagínate al acné que tú y yo conocemos
a secret of something that
un secreto de algo que me ha hecho a mí
my wife has done to me okay And now suddenly you only
mi mujer vale Y ahora de repente tú solo
count Peppa so that Peppa can tease me
cuentas a Peppa para que Peppa me pique
and Peppa sends me barbs the people in the
y Peppa me manda pullita la gente de la
audience don't know she doesn't get the barbs
audiencia no sabe la no pilla la puyitas
because you don't know what you're talking about
porque no sabes de lo que estás hablando
but I am asking for them then
pero yo sí las estoy pidiendo entonces
Marta jumps why Because she is catching
Marta salta por qué Porque está pillando
the [ __ ] that is being said to her  throwing I don't I do
la [__] que le están lanzando yo no yo
n't know
no sé
with the intention I have heard
con la intención Yo la he escuchado a
this tweeter who is now very offended
esta tuitera que está ahora muy ofendida
I have heard her get on a
Yo la he escuchado subirse a un canal de
YouTube channel this YouTube channel which is the Let's
YouTube a este canal de YouTube que es
say as the spokesperson for them no
el Digamos como el portavoz de ellas no
and and say things like yes to Marta she is
y y decir cosas como que sí a Marta está
Angry because in the end Antonio David
Rabiosa porque al final Antonio David se
can be found this weekend at
puede encontrar este fin de semana en
a wedding that is going and organ I don't know what And in the
una boda que va y órga no sé qué Y al
end Antonio David Marta well did not attend
final Antonio David Marta pues no acudía
that wedding because they are
a esa boda porque están
even yesterday I think it was that the attack
incluso ayer creo que fue que el ataque
on
a
Evita and so on is to go
Evita y demás es para para para ir en
against Olga
contra de Olga
Yes the youtuber said but it was you the
Sí el youtuber dijo pero Fuiste tú la
manipulation is that the youtuber
manipulación es que el youtuber traduce
always translates everything you know that he
siempre todo ya sabéis que de la
translates reality as he wants to
realidad la traduce como él lo quiere
interpret it let's see here the move is that
interpretar a ver aquí la movida es que
as I am telling you that this tweeter
como bien os estoy diciendo esa tuitera
has direct contact with a part of
tienen contacto directo con una parte de
the Moreno family with a person from the
la familia Moreno con una persona de la
Moreno family and this tweeter
familia Moreno y esa esta tuiteras
lets things go and they use her so that
suelta las cosas y la utilizan para que
luck already things because she is the typical one
suerte ya las cosas porque es la típica
like the everyday forum member no who
como la forera del cotidiano no que
have a life that is as it is and has
tienen una vida que es como es y tiene
an empty life and  needs to be educated
una vida vacía y necesita formarse
needs to feel part of something needs to
necesita sentirse parte de algo necesita
have her role not in history her
tener su papel no en la historia su
protagonism not for people to tell her oh
protagonismo no que la gente le diga Uy
this Keep this data you know I don't know what
esta Quédate de datos conoces no sé qué
And then of course there the relationship of
Y entonces claro ahí la relación de
messing with you avoid messing with Olga no
meterse con evitas meterse con Olga no
I don't even know if Olga knows
yo no sé ni siquiera ni si Olga sabrá
that this tablet is releasing so many
que esta tableta está soltando tantas
things that come to her from her
cosas que le vienen por parte de su
own family I understand I mean I thought
propia familia entiendo O sea yo pensaba
Olga doesn't know
que Olga no lo sabe
that she said that she practically discredited
que dijo que prácticamente desacreditó a
the sister a long long time ago but
la hermana hace ya mucho mucho pero
many months if I remember correctly
muchos meses si no recuerdo mal
then the sister didn't even know who
entonces la hermana no sabía ni quién
the lawyer was
era la abogada
subtly like Olga does subtly
sutilmente como lo hace Olga sutilmente
but she did it Yes Olga here what it was Yes it's
pero lo hizo Sí Olga aquí lo que fue Sí
true that is what it was
es verdad que es lo que fue
no to Olga I know that she doesn't
no a Olga a mí me consta que no le hace
like the things that the sister says on
gracia las cosas que dice la hermana en
social media and the behavior of the soul on social
redes y el comportamiento del alma en
media but much less I imagine that she would like
redes pero mucho menos me imagino yo que
that a tutor goes around saying
le gustará que una tutera ande diciendo
certain things you know I mean and it made me
ciertas cosas sabes o sea y a mí me hizo
laugh a lot the other day a tweeter from
mucha gracia el otro día un tuitero de
the blue tide who is one of the most
la marea azul que es uno de los más
powerful of the blue tide super
potentes de la marea azul súper
indignant who uses Olga I will be
indignado quien utiliza Olga estaré en
against the people that Olga uses
contra de las personas que utiliza Olga
and let's say I actually felt like it I
y vamos lo dije de hecho me entraron
said it in a video buddy when
ganas lo dije en un vídeo colega cuando
you were saying
usted estabais diciendo
when I started to say what
cuando yo empecé a decir lo que está
Antonio David Juan is saying now
diciendo Antonio David Juan ahora hace
a year and a half ago you all jumped on me and
un año y medio se me echasteis encima y
that same tweeter took the cap's side I
ese mismo tuitero se puso de parte del
already sent him a message I
Ya le puse un mensaje Yo a este Twitter
sent him a message to this Twitter a dm and I said
le puse un mensaje un md y le puse
good
bueno
read the bad no no no
leer lo malo no no no
Well
Bueno
you instead of getting angry you should
tú en vez de enfadarte tendrías que
be like this in the Barrier with some
estar así en la Barrera con unas
popcorn literally get
palomitas literalmente
pissed off have you seen that the best thing is
cabrearte tú has visto que lo mejor es
not to comment on anything about those people at all man
no comentar nada de esa gente nada tío
Because it's not that I'm losing subscribers
Porque ya no es que pierda suscriptores
money whatever it is it's that they overwhelm your
dinero lo que sea es que te agobian la
life and you give them the space they have
vida y le das el sitio que tiene
recognize them you know
reconozcan saben
you [ __ ]
tú cabrón
then you'll have to be like this now
entonces tú tendrás que estar así ahora
making your videos of things now I love it I
haciendo tus vídeos de cosas ahora me me
love that now for example this
me encanta que ahora por ejemplo este
tweeter who by the way Juanjo
tuitero que por cierto Juanjo lo
betrayed him and sent me a screenshot
traicionó y me mandó captura de pantalla
all the words for Antonio David
todas las palabras para Antonio David
Flores it's a video of yours yes from
flores es un vídeo tuyo sí de
a year ago
hace un año
and I put it to this tweeter I put the
y le pongo a este tuitero le pongo el
link and  I put You think it's
enlace y le pongo Tú crees que es
justice and he didn't answer me at
justicia y no me contestó absolutamente
all and now
nada y ahora
Juanjo sent me a screenshot of
Juanjo me mandó captura de pantalla de
that scissors David Flores from Juanjo blog
ese tijero David flores de Juanjo blog
Of course of course Juanjo sent me my
Claro claro Juanjo me mandó a mi captura
screenshot and I have it of that tweeter
de pantalla y lo tengo de ese tuitero
talking about
hablando
what Juanjo is saying, colleague, that
lo que está diciendo Juanjo colega que
you were on his side and six taxis
tú estabas de su parte y seis taxi
on me when I've been saying the same thing for a year and a
encima mía cuando yo llevo un año y
half but anyway
medio y poniendo lo mismo pero bueno
to finish this topic I won't give it
para terminar con este tema ya no darle
more prominence because it's true that there will be nothing
más protagonismo porque sí que es verdad
that I regret more
que no habrá cosa que me arrepienta más
in life than having worked side by side
en la vida de haber trabajado codo a
with these characters because if it
codo con estos personajes porque si no
weren't for me neither
fuera por mí ni lo conocerían los
journalists would know about it nor would it have the repercussions
periodistas ni tendría la repercusión
that it has nor would it surely have any of
que tiene ni tendría seguramente nada de
the attention and of and of people
la atención y de y de que la gente lo
knowing about it today but I
conozca a día de hoy pero
've drawn a blank with what I was going to say I was going to
me he quedado en blanco con lo que iba a
say to finish this
decir iba a decir para terminar con esto
popcorn
palomitas
The other day I heard you now of course as a
El otro día te escuché ahora claro a
result of these things all the videos come out
raíz de estas cosas me salen todos
and all the things that I'm not
vídeos y todas las cosas que no me estoy
complaining eh No don't misunderstand but and there
quejando eh No no malinterprete pero y
are times that I put it in the background of the
hay veces que lo pongo de fondo del
Hotel I heard you I don't know what  what
Hotel te escuché no sé en qué de que era
the video was about but you were telling people that they
el vídeo pero decías a la gente que se
were taking this too seriously
estaban tomando esto demasiado en serio
that we are giving importance to
que le estamos dando una importancia a
things that happen another one on TV with one with one
las cosas que pasan otro de la tele con
with an intensity that is not
una con una con una intensidad que no es
typical I think that the other day when I
propia Yo creo que el otro día cuando
spoke here it seems to me that by putting my
hablé aquí me parece que por meterme un
feet in the puddle a little I think I
poco los pies en el charco Este creo que
made my position quite clear I was not
dejé bastante Clara mi postura yo no
unaware that there were tides and
desconocía que hubiese de mareas y
cyclones and what and I think I made
ciclones y lo que y creo que dejé
my position quite clear apparently what
Clara mi postura por lo visto
I said did not sit very well with anyone That
no sentó muy bien uno lo que yo dijese
in the end people Look for nuclei
De que al final la gente Busca núcleos
that represent them because they feel
que le representen porque se sienten
part of something I am sorry that is an
parte de algo lo siento eso es una
absolute truth and it is evident and
verdad absoluta y es una evidencia y
secondly is that something is beginning to penetrate
segundo es que está empezando a calar
society that is very
una cosa en la sociedad que es muy
dangerous And that is that everything that is not
peligrosa Y es que todo lo que no sea
radical
radical
[Music]
[Música]